<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Anime Quotes</string>

    <string name="affirmation0">
        "The world isn't perfect. But it's there for us, doing the best it can....that's what makes it so damn beautiful."
        ~ Roy Mustang (Full Metal Alchemist)
    </string>
    <string name="affirmation1">
       "To know sorrow is not terrifying. What is terrifying is to know you can't go back to happiness you could have."
~ Matsumoto Rangiku (Bleach)
    </string>
    <string name="affirmation2">
        "We are all like fireworks: we climb, we shine and always go our separate ways and become further apart. But even when that time comes, let's not disappear like a firework and continue to shine.. forever."
~ Hitsugaya Toshiro (Bleach)
    </string>
    <string name="affirmation3">
       "Those who stand at the top determine what's wrong and what's right! This very place is neutral ground! Justice will prevail, you say? But of course it will! Whoever wins this war becomes justice!"
~ Don Quixote Doflamingo (One Piece)
    </string>
    <string name="affirmation4">
       "Fear is not evil. It tells you what weakness is. And once you know your weakness, you can become stronger as well as kinder."

~Gildarts Clive (Fairy Tail)
    </string>
    <string name="affirmation5">
        Fear is freedom! Subjugation is liberation! Contradiction is truth! Those are the facts of this world! And you will all surrender to them, you pigs in human clothing!"

~ Satsuki Kiryuuin (Kill la Kill)
    </string>
    <string name="affirmation6">
       "I am the hope of the universe. I am the answer to all living things that cry out for peace. I am protector of the innocent. I am the light in the darkness. I am truth. Ally to good! Nightmare to you!"
    </string>
    <string name="affirmation7">
        “Thinking you’re no-good and worthless is the worst thing you can do”

~ Nobito (Doraemon)
    </string>
    <string name="affirmation8">
       "Religion, ideology, resources, land, spite, love or just because… No matter how pathetic the reason, it’s enough to start war. War will never cease to exist… reasons can be thought up after the fact… Human nature pursues strife."
~ Paine (Naruto Shippuden)
    </string>
    <string name="affirmation9">
       “Don’t give up, there’s no shame in falling down! True shame is to not stand up again!”

~ Shintaro Midorima (Kuroko No Basket)
    </string>
</resources>